var questions = [
    {
        question: "The Mandalorian's armor is made of what material?",
        choices: {
            a: "Steel",
            b: "Titanium",
            c: "Cobalt",
            d: "Beskar"
        },
        correctAnswer: "b"
    },
    {
        question: "Would you give your life for Baby Yoda?",
        choices: {
            a: "Absolutely",
            b: "Nope",
            c: "I wanna live",
            d: "Nah"
        },
        correctAnswer: "Absolutely"
    },
    {
        question: "What weapon does the Mandalorian have on his left wrist?",
        choices: {
            a: "Knife",
            b: "Flamethrower",
            c: "Taser",
            d: "A blaster"
        },
        correctAnswer: "Flamethrower"
    },
    {
        question: "What is the Mandalorian's moral code?",
        choices: {
            a: "Hooyah",
            b: "Rangers Lead the Way",
            c: "Get some",
            d: "This is the way"
        },
        correctAnswer: "This is the way"
    },
    {
        question: "Who does Mando hunt down in order to get his stolen spaceship parts back from?",
        choices:  {
            a: "Jawas",
            b: "Tusken Raiders",
            c: "Stormtroopers",
            d: "Jedi"
        },
        correctAnswer: "Jawas"
    },
    {
        question: "How many years post-Empire does the Mandalorian take place?",
        choices:  {
            a: "28",
            b: "11",
            c: "20",
            d: "5"
        },
        correctAnswer: "5"
    },
    {
        question: "What are the Mandalorians known for?",
        choices:  {
            a: "Pod-racing",
            b: "Smuggling",
            c: "Bounty hunting",
            d: "Blue milk"
        },
        correctAnswer: "Bounty hunting"
    },
    {
        question: "What group is Mando a part of?",
        choices:  {
            a: "The First Order",
            b: "The Guild",
            c: "The Mos Eisley Cantina Band",
            d: "Jabba The Hutt's Gang"
        },
        correctAnswer: "The Guild"
    },
    {
        question: "Who does the Empire want Mando to find for them?",
        choices:  {
            a: "Kylo Ren",
            b: "Greedo",
            c: "Baby Yoda",
            d: "Wicket the Ewok"
        },
        correctAnswer: "Baby Yoda"
    },
    {
        question: "What character threatens to initiate self-destruct in episode 1?",
        choices:  {
            a: "IG-11, the assasin droid",
            b: "Yub Nub",
            c: "Bossk",
            d: "Boba Fett"
        },
        correctAnswer: "IG-11"
    },
    {
        question: "What can't a Mandalorian do?",
        choices:  {
            a: "Work with others",
            b: "Kill enemies",
            c: "Remove his helmet",
            d: "Shoot first"
        },
        correctAnswer: "Remove his helmet"
    },
]

var score = 0;

for (var i = 0; i < questions.length; i++) {
    var response = w
}